HameFura, I Reincarnated
into an
Otome Game
as a
Villainess
with only
destruction flags···
aimaina I my me datte guruguru mazetara
If you mix it round and round it becomes unclear
akogare no kyuu tenkai ni niau kamo ne
With an unexpected development, maybe it will look good
ren ai nara iza morase
If it's love, express it now
tobikiri no dessert
with wonderful desserts
amazuppai cho misu wa oyurushi asobase
An addictive sweet and sour mix, I'm sorry to have fun
mawaru uruwashiki koi moyou
Love is a spiral pattern that spins on and on
chotto souzou naname you he massugu susume
I need to stop and think before moving forward
otome no route wa hitotsu janai
A maiden's route is not just one!
hatto suru lucky na ima ni gokigen you
My heart feels surprisingly lucky now
itsudatte maemukina desu
And so I will remain optimistic
ai mo kawarazu ni touhonseisou kou kando wo agete
If you want to win the game of love, you have to risk it all
kiyoku tadashiku utsukushiku are to wa yoku itta monda na
It's a pure, intense and beautiful feeling, so fight for it
kitto warui happy na mirai ni gokigen you
I still don't know if my ending will be happy or not
itsu datte maemukina desu
But I will remain optimistic
Episode 11
The Moment of My Doom Arrived... Part 2
I swear...
How long are you going to keep sleeping, you fool?!
Wh... What?
Don't "What?" me!
I called you a dozen times,
and you didn't wake up.
You're going to be late to school again.
Huh? Mother?
"Mother"?
Uh, wha...
Come on, snap out of it and get ready for school!
And make sure you fix your hair!
Isn't there anything I can do about these cowlicks?
Anne usually makes my hair look nice for me...
Huh? Wait, who is this Anne again?
Is this what I've always looked like?
Oh, crap!
When are you going to learn to wake up
without having your blanket dragged off of you?
Shouldn't you be at college, Onii-chan?
My classes start in the afternoon.
Here's your lunch.
Thanks!
Okay, now get going.
Right! See you later!
Wait! Why did you take that?!
If you have to eat on the run,
at least take bread or something!
Have a good day.
Just barely safe!
Nope, unfortunately. You're out.
Someone in my class told me you
got called out for coming in late.
Yeah, I was up a little too late last night.
I had trouble getting up this morning.
You were playing games all night again, weren't you?
You should try to manage your time better.
So, how far have you gotten in Fortune Lover?
I'm about to conquer the self-centered Prince Alan.
But I've been able to talk normally with him and enjoy it,
so he doesn't really seem that self-centered.
He's generally pretty nice.
Nice?
Wait... huh? What am I talking about?
Uh, never mind!
We should hurry up and eat!
I missed breakfast, so I'm really hungry.
You can have my rolled omelet, then.
Thanks, Acchan-sama! I'll eat it right now!
So good!
The usual routine...
Every day is the same as always...
Yet for some reason, it all feels so nostalgic
and precious.
Still...
I feel as if I'm forgetting something important...
She's been asleep for two whole days.
And we don't even know why!
This latest doctor is the most intelligent
and advanced one in the country.
I'm sure he'll figure out what's going on.
Everyone, please come in.
What do you think?
Frankly, I have no idea what's causing this.
I've examined her all over,
and nothing is physically wrong.
She may wake up at any moment,
or she may never wake up again.
Oh, no!
What will happen to her if she never wakes up?
If she just continues to sleep for the rest of her life,
I suppose she'll grow weaker and eventually die.
No! You can't be serious!
Keith-sama!
Catarina-sama...
Catarina-sama, please... please...
Please don't leave me...
Are you all right?
Yes... I'm sorry.
I'll go and do the cleaning.
Of course.
I'll keep an eye on Catarina.
Thank you.
Catarina...
Besides, this is just a scratch.
It's nothing to worry about.
When that strange little girl came into my life,
her bizarre behavior drew my interest.
And as I spent time with you,
the dull, gray world I had been living in
became filled with brilliant colors.
Before that, all I ever knew was boredom,
and everything felt tedious.
I knew nothing of happiness or pleasure,
and you taught all that to me.
Jealousy and loneliness, too.
Everything.
I knew danger was near,
and yet I couldn't protect you.
We're brother and sister now.
You can call me "Sister."
I remember it as if it was just yesterday.
I was called a monster,
sat huddled up in a dark room,
and lived my life all alone.
And then she smiled at me.
With her warm hand,
she led me into a much brighter world.
That was when I made a vow
to become stronger so that
I could be the one to protect her.
And yet...
Why wasn't I by her side when she needed me?
Your green thumb makes you extra special
and extra amazing, Mary!
I still clearly remember
the day I met Catarina-sama.
I was a weakling and a coward,
always looking down, always running away.
But Catarina-sama said I was special...
that I was amazing.
I am who I am now because
Catarina-sama was by my side.
Because she loved me
and said I was important.
I hated myself, but she
made me love who I was.
I want to continue to be with her forever.
With the one I love,
who's so precious to me...
I'm sure you have some of each, as well.
We all have things we handle well and things we don't.
That's what she said to me when I was
sulking over being constantly
compared to my twin brother.
She never held back when competing with me
and always faced me head-on.
After I met her,
I was finally able to loosen the excess
tension I'd been putting on my shoulders.
Being next to someone as honest
and straightforward as her
made me feel so comfortable.
So I stayed beside her, as if it was
the most natural thing in the world.
I'm scared of losing her!
How could I be so oblivious?
Why did it take me until now
to realize how I feel?!
With such lovely parents
and such an adorable sister,
you truly are blessed, Nicol-sama.
People decided that a precious
member of my family was a jinx,
and took pity on me.
No matter how many times I told them
I was happy, no one understood.
I had decided that no one
would ever understand,
that I should just give up.
But Catarina, and only Catarina, understood.
When anger and frustration flooded my heart,
she embraced it with her warmth.
From that day on,
Catarina was someone special to me.
But she's engaged to my childhood
friend, the third prince.
I know I can't be with her forever,
no matter how I feel about her.
But still, I wanted to stay close
to her as long as possible.
Don't go anywhere, Catarina.
Your white hair is as beautiful as silk,
and your red eyes twinkle like rubies.
I think they're both beautiful!
For my whole life,
people called me "creepy"
and "cursed" because of my looks.
But Catarina-sama said I was pretty
and asked me to be her friend.
She was the first friend I ever had.
Her smile was so kind...
My life then changed in a tremendous way.
I left the room I had
spent my life locked away in
and stepped into the bright sun.
I thought being so happy
every day was like a dream
that only ever happened in books,
but then I was living it.
But now...
Catarina-sama, I don't want to lose you!
I couldn't bear that!
That's right! I refuse to lose her again!
Who was that?
I finally managed to find her!
I won't lose her again!
That voice...
I'm going to save her this time.
So don't just sit around in here crying.
You have to take me to her!
I am Catarina-sama's best friend, Mary Hunt!
I'm not a weakling like those other noble ladies!
What am I doing, sitting around in here?
I have to save my sister!
She saved me.
Now it's my turn.
Sophia-sama?
I want to stay with Catarina-sama
until she awakens!
I'm staying with my sister, too!
I won't leave Catarina-sama's side, either!
Me, neither.
I'll keep talking to her until she wakes up!
Everyone...
Please, I beg you...
Save Catarina-sama.
I'm on it! I'll bring her back, I promise!
All of you, just stay there and keep calling to her!
Acchan, I'm finally here!
Yes.
I'm working on conquering the
black-hearted, sadistic prince now.
I can't seem to make any
progress with him, though.
I see.
So... how's school going?
Are you having fun?
Huh? Yeah.
What brought that on, anyway?
I'm having a lot of fun.
I'm glad I was able to find you again
and spend time with you.
But the thing is...
This isn't your world anymore, is it?
Acchan?
Your world is somewhere else now.
There are a lot of people waiting for you there.
Listen. They're all calling for you.
Catarina! Catarina!
Please wake up!
I can't even imagine life without you anymore!
Wake up, Sister!
Didn't you promise you'd always be with me?!
Catarina-sama, I can't do my best
at anything without you!
Are you just gonna sleep forever?!
Wake up already, you dumb rich girl!
Wake up, Catarina!
Please open your eyes, Catarina-sama!
Please wake up, Catarina-sama!
Why... did I forget?
My family can be annoying,
but they're so kind.
I have a close otaku friend
and a beloved otome game...
This world feels comfortable to be in.
But...
I have to go back!
To the world where all
the people I love are waiting for me!
That's it! Acchan!
I bet you know where Maria is, right?
Maria is on the school grounds.
There's a hidden room in the school storehouse.
Also, why did the student
council president—
I know you can fix this.
Save the president,
just like you saved all of us.
His real name is...
Acchan!
This is probably the last time I'll ever see Acchan.
My best friend ever since middle school...
She's helped me out so much
but because of that accident,
I didn't have a chance
to thank her or say goodbye.
Acchan! I'm so glad I got to see you again!
Goodbye!
Thank you so much for always being there!
I was truly happy, too.
This time, I'll always be by your side...
as Sophia.
Goodbye, and thank you,
my precious best friend.
Don't cry, Sophia.
Good morning.
Welcome back, Catarina-sama!
Catarina-sama!
I was so, so worried about you!
This is my world.
I want to protect this world
and the people I care about.
I won't let that bad ending happen!
I'm going to save Maria!
Huh?
Catarina, we still don't know where she's gone.
She's on the school grounds,
in a hidden room in the storehouse.
What are you talking about, sis?
How do you know where she is?
Oh, uh...
It came to me in a dream!
Huh?
The student council president
was the one who cast the sleep spell on me.
He took Maria away, too.
Sirius Dieke? It was him?
Why would Sirius do that?
He's where Maria is.
Maria is safe.
Did that come to you in a dream, too?
No.
It's my intuition!
I can't believe the president has magic
that can manipulate people.
I thought he was such a kind person... Why?
I'm honestly not sure, either.
That's it.
The Dieke family built the storehouse,
but it's supposed to be essentially unused now.
There really is a hidden room...
Maria!
Catarina-sama... and everyone!
I'm sorry we took so long, Maria!
I should apologize for putting
you all through so much trouble.
No, don't apologize.
I know you did it for my sake.
Thank you, Maria.
So... what about the president?
Is he still here?
Yes.
Are you already aware of what he's done?
I know the gist of it,
but there's lot I don't understand about it.
That's why I want to talk to him one more time.
You know, the tea you make...
has a very gentle flavor.
The tea you make has such a gentle flavor.
I sense a human presence.
You must not be caught here!
It's over.
The moment of my doom has come!
Not yet!
You have not completed your revenge yet!
Have you forgotten the last
words your mother said to you?!
Mom! Mom!
Please... avenge me.
Eliminate them all...
using your dark magic.
No! If I do that...
Are you okay, Maria?
Yes... I sense incredible power.
Sirius Dieke!
You?
What are you doing here?
kokoro ga tsukiru made moyase
My heart yearns for you so much
kantan ni clear dekiru
I thought it was easy to clear
koi wa game sou omotteta
To win at this love game
gururi madowasete hikiyosete
I'm spinning around and pulling you in
otosu shudai wo narabuke wo
Following along in my footsteps
naze kimi dakara igai
Why are you so captivating?
dono route erabeba saita nano ka
Which route will be the best choice?
kotae wa mienai
I can't find the answer
Bad End no unmei demo boku no mono ni nareba ii
Even if fate leads me to a "Bad End", it's fine
sou saa douse hametsu suru no nara kimi to
You're the one I want in my life
zettai ni zetsumei shinai aida to chikaukara
My love for you will never change
ubai saa nareru kakugo
Prepare to be conquered
mubou mi de muteki nayosashisa mudai makichirasu mae ni
You make me feel invincible, imprudent and happy at the same time
sono chisen wo hitorijime shitte miseru
I want to find out more about you
donna kodoku mo itami mo
No matter how much the pain is
kimi goto uketomeru
I will carry it for you
machi ukeru zetsubou mo nozomu tokoro
Even if despair awaits me, I'll take it on